

tonyly.com

**4**25-343-3711

**♀** Kirkland, WA, 98033

## **EDUCATION**

## **SUMMARY**

2016 University of New

England College of Pharmacy

PharmD

University of

Washington
BS Microbiology

Newly licensed pharmacist in Washington state. Possesses seven years of pharmacy experience in a community setting. Excellent interpersonal skills drives desire to build long-lasting relationships with patients, pharmacy colleagues, and fellow medical professionals. Seeking a pharmacist position that will provide the opportunity to practice high-quality, patient-centered health care.

## **SKILLS**

 $\textbf{PHARMACY INFORMATICS TOOLS:} \ \text{GNU/Linux, MS-DOS, R, Python, Sublime Text, SQL}$ 

**ELECTRONIC HEALTH RECORD SOFTWARE:** Epic, Meditech, GE Centricity

GENERAL COMPUTER SKILLS: Microsoft Windows, OS X, MS Word, MS Excel, MS PowerPoint, 85 WPM

### **EMPLOYMENT**

### **CAREERSTAFF RX**

Seattle, WA Dec 2016 to Present

**Pharmacist Graduate Intern** 

- Advocate for patients to ensure they receive appropriate treatment while minimizing costs
- Answer clinical drug information questions from patients and pharmacy staff
- Assist in verifying accurate antibiotic dosing and dose intervals
- Provide patient education on proper medication usage and common side effects

### TARGET PHARMACY

Redmond, WA Aug 2007 to Aug 2014

Pharmacist Intern; Pharmacy Assistant

- Answered clinical drug information questions from patients and pharmacy staff
- Assisted in verifying accurate antibiotic dosing and dose intervals
- Interpreted prescriptions for patients via electronic patient profiles to minimize risk of DDIs and to identify possible contraindications
- Interprofessional collaboration with prescribers via telephone to ensure accurate and appropriate therapy to patients
- Prepared oral antibiotic suspensions for patients
- Provided patient education on proper medication usage and possible side effects

### UNIVERSITY OF WASHINGTON, DEPT OF PHARMACEUTICS

Seattle, WA Jun 2010 to Aug 2012

Research Technician II (Lin Lab)

- Primary research in identifying endogenous biomarkers for cytochrome P450 metabolism
- Extracted compounds of interest from human biological specimen via liquid-liquid extractions
- Conducted biological sample analysis via High-Performance Liquid Chromatography-Tandem Mass Spectrometry (HPLC/MS-MS)
- Compiled metabolomics database using Quadrupole-Time of Flight (Q-TOF) instrumentation

### **PROJECTS**

#### VANCOMYCIN THERAPEUTIC DOSING AND MONITORING PROGRAM

May 2015 to Aug 2015

Conducted retrospective outcomes evaluation on pharmacist-driven vancomycin dosing and monitoring protocols in inpatient and acute care settings. Spearheaded data analysis enhancement with pharmacy informatics integration to automate data collection.

# PROFESSIONAL LICENSURE